snowcovered.com 2012-05-10

# DotNetNuke Store Home

DotNetNuke The Store is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the DotNetNuke The Store Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the DotNetNuke The Store website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.  

DotNetNuke The Store is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the DotNetNuke The Store Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the DotNetNuke The Store website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

  Collection of your Personal Information

  DotNetNuke The Store collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. DotNetNuke The Store also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by DotNetNuke The Store. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by DotNetNuke The Store for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the DotNetNuke The Store Web site.

  Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through DotNetNuke The Store public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: DotNetNuke The Store does not read any of your private online communications.

DotNetNuke The Store encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from DotNetNuke The Store so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. DotNetNuke The Store is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the DotNetNuke The Store and DotNetNuke The Store family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

DotNetNuke The Store collects and uses your personal information to operate the DotNetNuke The Store Web site and deliver the services you have requested. DotNetNuke The Store also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from DotNetNuke The Store and its affiliates. DotNetNuke The Store may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

  DotNetNuke The Store does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. DotNetNuke The Store may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of other users. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, DotNetNuke The Store may share your contact data with other users whom you have initiated communications with using the web site services; from commercial or non-commercial activity.

  DotNetNuke The Store does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

  DotNetNuke The Store keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within DotNetNuke The Store, in order to determine what DotNetNuke The Store services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within DotNetNuke The Store to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

  DotNetNuke The Store Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on DotNetNuke The Store or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DotNetNuke The Store; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DotNetNuke The Store, or the public.

  Use of Cookies

  The DotNetNuke The Store Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

  One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize DotNetNuke The Store pages, or register with DotNetNuke The Store site or services, a cookie helps DotNetNuke The Store to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same DotNetNuke The Store Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the DotNetNuke The Store features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the DotNetNuke The Store services or Web sites you visit.

  Security of your Personal Information

  DotNetNuke The Store secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. DotNetNuke The Store secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

  Changes to this Statement

  DotNetNuke The Store will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. DotNetNuke The Store encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how DotNetNuke The Store is protecting your information.

  Contact Information

  DotNetNuke The Store welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DotNetNuke The Store has not adhered to this Statement, please contact DotNetNuke The Store at store@dnncorp.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
